来吧，红
Come on, Red. Giddyup.
快起来，来吧。骑他们吧，牛仔。
Giddyup, come on. Ride 'em, cowboy.
我们去抓那些亡命之徒。
Let's get those outlaws.
快到了。来吧!
We're almost there. Come on!
明白了。我们知道了。快到了。
Got it. We got it. We're almost there.
来吧。
Come on.
嘿,博伊德。
Hey, Boyd.
你在玉米地里待了多久?
How long were you out in the corn?
我希望不是又一整晚。
Not all night again, I hope.
我不想让你再哭了，伊登。
I don't want you to cry anymore, Eden.
别担心，伊登。
Don't worry, Eden.
在玉米地里什么都不会死。
Nothing ever really dies in the corn.
博伊德!该死的。你到底去哪儿了?
Boyd! Damn it. Where the hell you been?
博伊德……博伊德,不!
Boyd... Boyd, no!
各单位注意，瑞尔斯通儿童之家发生人质劫持事件。
All units be advised, there is a hostage situation at the Rylstone Children's Home.
当地治安官和他的农民朋友们使用了一种动物镇静气体试图解决这个问题。
The local sheriff and his farmer buddies have used some kind of animal sedative gas to try and solve it.
从所有报道来看，这听起来像是一场灾难。
By all reports, it sounds like a total disaster.
是的，我现在在这里。
Yeah, I'm here now.
这些白痴简直是在往里面灌氟烷想把这孩子弄死。
These idiots are literally pumping halothane in to try to take this kid down.
好吧，我的连任失败了。
Well, there goes my reelection.
唯一的一线希望就是那个该死的太空学员。
The only silver lining is that goddamn space cadet in there.
那个小矮子在玉米地里游荡了四天才有人意识到她不是毒气的受害者之一。
That little runt was wandering around the corn for four days before anybody realized she wasn't one of the casualties from the goddamn gas.
牧师，看看那孩子有没有说过什么能解释他为什么突然发作，杀了那么多人。
Pastor, try and find out if that boy said anything that would explain why he snapped and killed all those people.
所以…
So...
我猜这就是说，经历了这一切之后，你需要一个住的地方，对吧?
I guess it follows that, uh, you'll need a place to live after all this, huh?
谁知道呢?
Who knows?
如果你是个好女孩，也许我们可以让你来和我住在一起。
If you're a good girl, then maybe we could manage it for you to come and live with me.
我有个马厩，里面有几匹老马。
I have a stable with a couple of old nags in it.
你可以挑一辆骑上去。
You can pick one out and ride it.
听起来怎么样?
How's that sound?
该死的!
God dang it!
这件衣服快把我逼疯了!
This one piece is driving me nuts!
哦。
Oh.
她来了。红方王后。
There she is. The Red Queen.
你喜欢红方王后吗?
You like the Red Queen?
红皇后让世界变成她想要的样子。
The Red Queen makes the world the way she wants it to be.
E-Eden,我……我真的很抱歉发生在家里的那些小朋友身上的事。
E-Eden, I'm... I'm really sorry about what happened to all your little friends in the home.
真的。
I really am.
这是个不幸的意外。
It was an unfortunate accident.
我得问你…那个男孩，他说什么了吗?
I-I have to ask you... That boy, did he say anything?
不。不是真的。
No. Not really.
除了说他很抱歉。
Oh, uh, except just to say he was sorry.
抱歉?
Sorry?
抱歉杀了监狱里的所有成年人?
Sorry for killing every adult in the facility?
不。
No.
我觉得他很抱歉没把你们都杀了。
I think he was sorry for not killing all of you.
嘿!回来!
Hey! Get back!
嘿，你怎么了?!
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
这应该是公开的!
That should be public!
酷。
Cool.
看看这些东西。
Look at this stuff.
我警告过他们多少次了?
How many times did I try and warn them?
他们都没看一眼标签就把这些东西埋在地里。
The stuff that they put into this ground without even barely reading a label.
有没有注意到“玉米”和“迷宫”这两个词…就像玉米和拼图……是一样的吗?
Ever notice how the words "maize" and "maze"... Like a corn maize and a puzzle... are the same?
玉米迷宫。
A maze of maize.
奇怪,是吧?
Weird, huh?
当然。“惊人的”。
Sure. "Amazing."
Har-dee-har。咬我。
Har-dee-har. Bite me.
嘿!
Hey!
毒素在腐烂作物的茎叶上生长。
Toxins grow on the stalks and leaves of rotting crops.
这是一种真菌。
It's a fungus.
它会让你生病甚至死亡。
It can make you sick or even die.
是的。
Yeah.
还有幻觉。
And, uh, hallucinations.
-随你怎么说，波。——什么?这是真的。
- Whatever you say, Bo. - What? It's true.
有人说它是塞勒姆女巫审判的罪魁祸首。
You know, some people say it was responsible for the Salem witch trials.
我也很高兴和你聊天，姐姐。
Fun talking to you too, sis.
啊!
Ahh!
嗯!闻闻那些毒素。天鹅绒般柔软可口。
Mmm! Smell those toxins. Velvety and delicious.
-太好了。-茜茜，别说了。
- So good. - Ceece, stop.
我想再来一份。
Think I'll have a second helping.
别说了。别玩那些东西了，好吗?
Cut it out. Stop playing with that stuff, okay?
现在，听我说。我…这不是我带你来的原因，好吗?
Now, listen to me. I... That's not why I brought you out here, okay?
这是。
This is.
我已经一个月没睡了，因为我…
I literally haven't been able to sleep for a month because I...
在这里。
Here.
我下周离开。
I leave next week.
听着，这是微生物学的本科学位。
Look, it's an undergraduate degree in microbiology.
好吧?这不是永恒。
All right? It's not an eternity.
它是。
It is.
它是!你为什么要回来?
It is! Why would you ever come back?
我知道你讨厌这里。
I know you hate it here.
因为。
Because.
因为你。因为爸爸。
Because of you. Because of Dad.
听着，希希，你知道，总有一天你也会离开这里。
And look, Ceece, you know, you'll leave here one day too.
因为我糟糕的成绩?
With my cruddy grades?
我将永远被困在这里。
I'll be stuck here forever.
在这个恐怖垂死的地方。
In this creepy, dying place.
不。瑞尔斯通不会死的。
No. Rylstone's not dying.
这几年过得很艰难。你知道吗?
It's been a hard couple years. You know?
我们犯了很多错误。
A lot of mistakes have been made.
做了很多糟糕透顶的决定。
A lot of shitty, shitty decisions.
但与…花点时间和心思，然后这一切…这是可以解决的。
But with... with a little time and care, then all this... it can be fixed.
是的。
Yeah.
听起来不错，波。
Sounds awesome, Bo.
Eden!天啊，你吓死我们了。
Eden! God, you scared the shit out of us.
认真对待。
Seriously.
假发是怎么回事?
What's with the wig?
今天我是红方王后。
Today I am the Red Queen.
Crud。
Crud.
说到这个我们走吧
Um, speaking of which let's go.
加油，红魔!快起来，来吧。
Come on, Red! Giddyup, come on.
塞西尔，你不会想错过这个的。
Cecil, you're not gonna want to miss this.
沃利·托马斯·普拉特!
Wally Thomas Pratt!
“因为残忍和不寻常地对待你自己的猎犬，你被判处死刑!”
"For the crime of cruel and unusual treatment of your very own hunting dog, you are hereby sentenced to die!"
你杀了吉伯!
You killed Gibber!
嘿!我知道这只是玩玩，但那不是我的错。
Hey! I know this is for play and all, but that wasn't my fault.
我没有给吉伯下毒药。
I didn't give Gibber that poison.
他从捕鼠器里吃的。
He ate it out of some rat trap.
而你却眼睁睁看着他受苦!
And you just watched him suffer!
他只是一只老猎狗。
He was just an old hound dog.
骗子!比利巴!
Liar! Billy Barnes!
狗的杀手!
Dog killer!
嘿,沃利。
Hey, Wally.
去你的，巴恩斯。
Screw you, Barnes.
滚下去，沃利!
Off the edge, Wally!
♬走独木桥，走独木桥♬
♪ Walk the plank, walk the plank ♪
♪走跳板，Wally Thomas Pratt♪
♪ Walk the plank, Wally Thomas Pratt ♪
♬走独木桥，走独木桥♬
♪ Walk the plank, walk the plank ♪
♪走跳板，Wally Thomas Pratt♪
♪ Walk the plank, Wally Thomas Pratt ♪
噢!呀!该死，比利，别用那东西戳我!
Ow! Jeez! Dang it, Billy, quit jabbing me with that thing!
放弃拖延!结束了!
Quit stalling! Off the end!
结束了!
Off the end!
跳!跳!跳!跳!
Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
跳!
Jump!
照他们说的做!跳!
Do what they say! Jump!
来吧!
Come on!
嘿!你到底在干什么?
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
嘿,考尔德。
Hey, Calder.
你在我奶奶的车上做什么?
What in frick's name are you doing on my grandma's car?
凸轮吗?
Cam?
下车。滚远点。
Get off. Get the hell off.
你疯了吗?
Are you effing crazy?
你们这些蠢蛋。
You dumb-ass idiots.
你把四分之一的嵌板弄凹了。
You've dented the quarter panels.
你把窗户打碎了。
You cracked the window.
该死的。
Damn.
你甚至把油箱都弄坏了。
You've even busted the gas tank.
等等，考尔德，这是你的车?
Wait, Calder, this is your car?
是的。我的奶奶的。66岁的。
Yeah. My grandma's. '66 Olds.
那为什么要停在这荒郊野外?
So why is it parked out here in the middle of nowhere?
管好你的事怎么样，derp?
How about mind your business, derp?
我想把我奶奶的车停在我爸的地里，我会的，好吗?
I want to park my grandma's car in my dad's field, I will, okay?
你到底在外面干什么?
What the hell are you doing out here anyway?
我们要处决沃利·普拉特。
We're executing Wally Pratt.
他让吉伯痛苦而漫长地死去。
He let Gibber die a long and painful death.
胡扯?不可能。我爱吉伯。
Gibber? No way. I loved Gibber.
螺丝。
Screw that.
和他的混蛋在一起。
Off the edge with his punk ass.
是啊!现在，别再拖延了!
Yeah! Now, quit stalling!
从边缘掉下来!
Off the edge!
——是的!-从边缘掉下来!
- Yeah! - Off the edge!
跳!
Jump!
该死，比利!
Dang it, Billy!
阿奇，准备在他落地时点燃玉米。
Archie, get ready to light up that corn when he lands in it.
哇!等待。你不能这么做。
Whoa! Wait. You can't do that.
那辆车在漏油，空气中弥漫着谷物粉尘?
With that car leaking gas and the grain dust in the air?
那东西就像火药，知道吗?
That stuff is like gunpowder, okay?
什么都不剩了，包括你。
There won't be anything left, including you.
是的。博林是对的。把他推开。
Yeah. Boleyn's right. Just shove him off.
我们假装把他烧死!
We'll pretend the part where we burn him to death!
是啊!
Yeah!
死亡!死亡!死亡!
Death! Death! Death!
从边缘掉下来!
Off the edge!
-把他推下去!-从边缘掉下来!
- Push him off! - Off the edge!
-我不干了。-从边缘掉下来!
- I'm out. - Off the edge!
-从边缘掉下来!-从边缘掉下来!
- Off the edge! - Off the edge!
走跳板!
Walk the plank!
哇!
Whoo!
从边缘掉下来!走跳板!
Off the edge! Walk the plank!
-你在开玩笑吧?-从边缘掉下来!
- You're kidding, right? - Off the edge!
-你开玩笑吧?——什么?他们也是我的朋友。
- You're kidding? - What? They're my friends too.
下周你走后，可能是我唯一的朋友。
And after you leave next week, probably my only friends.
走跳板!走跳板!
Walk the plank! Walk the plank!
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo !
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo!
哇!
Whoo!
死亡!死亡!
Death! Death!
嘿。
Hey.
菠，自从我们上次玩海盗之后，发生了很多变化。
A lot's changed since the last time we played pirates, Bo.
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的,是的。我只是…
Yeah, yeah. I'm just...
听着，我觉得小家伙们吸入了太多腐烂的玉米真菌。
Look, I think the little ones have just been breathing in too much rotting corn fungus.
在这里也不难。
Wouldn't be hard around here.
你想解释一下那辆车吗?
So do you want to explain the car?
天啊，菠，非要我给你解释清楚吗?
Jeez, Bo, do I really have to spell it out for you?
我是说，如果是w-e-e-d就不是了。
I mean, not if it's spelled w-e-e-d.
玉米都快死了。
Corn's all dying.
还不如用这些地种点什么。
Might as well use these fields to grow something.
我上周满18岁了，菠。
I turned 18 last week, Bo.
我和你一样在建造一座桥。
I'm building a bridge just like you.
我要离开这里。
I'm getting out of here.
是的。
Yeah.
但你要逃的不只是莱尔斯通的死玉米，对吧?
Except it's not just Rylstone's dying corn you're escaping, is it?
别胡扯了。
Come off it.
这是个意外。
It was an accident.
卡尔，你不是…当我笨手笨脚地把他的拳头插在弟弟和他之间时，我的脸撞到了他的拳头。
Cal, you're not... My face hit his fist when I inserted it stupidly between my little brother and him.
事故。
Accident.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
不要。
Don't be.
为那些没有出路的人感到遗憾。
Be sorry for the ones who don't have a way out.
听着，说到出去…上个周末上学前。
Look, speaking of getting out... Last weekend before school.
你和其他人一起去河边了吗?
You headed to the river with everyone else?
不。
No.
我得留下来，照看我的投资。
I got to hang back, look after my investments.
看来你和我最后一次可以独享瑞尔斯通了。
Guess you and I will be having Rylstone all to ourselves one last time.
只有我们和小家伙们。
Just us and the little ones.
不要忘记那些小事。
Don't forget the little ones.
再见。
See you.
-走跳板!——上帝!
- Walk the plank! - God!
耶稣,什么…塞勒姆女巫审判已经结束了吗?
Jesus, what... So are the Salem witch trials over already?
非常甜蜜。沃利吓坏了。
It was pretty sweet. Wally was freaking out.
每个人都在尖叫，大喊大叫，在玉米地里跳舞。
Everybody was screaming and yelling and shouting and dancing through the corn.
真是太棒了。
It was pretty dope.
妈妈?
Mom?
Ceece。我们走吧。来吧。
Ceece. Let's go. Come on.
希希，这是爸爸妈妈之间的事。
Ceece, that's between Mom and Dad.
好吧?Ceece。来吧。
Okay? Ceece. Come on.
波，你太瞎了。
Bo, you are so blind.
这和妈妈无关。
It's not about Mom.
这和爸爸无关。
It's not about Dad.
是关于瑞尔斯通的。
It's about Rylstone.
而是关于这个地方已经支离破碎了甚至没有人愿意去修复它。
It's about this place that's so broken that nobody even gives a damn enough to try to fix it.
不过，我想这就不是你的问题了，对吧，菠?
But, then, I guess that's not your problem anymore, is it, Bo?
享受波士顿。
Enjoy Boston.
玉米……我们的玉米…正在消亡。
Corn... our corn... is dying.
-是的。-是的。
- Yeah. - Yeah.
在离这里不到500码的田野里，放眼望去，是一片垂死的棕色海洋。
In the fields not 500 yards from here, as far as the eye can see, is a sea of dying brown.
那些伴随我们长大的，祖先种在这里的金色谷物去哪了?
What happened to the glorious golden grain that we grew up with, that our forefathers planted here?
我们知道发生了什么。
Well, we know what happened.
我们投票了，大多数人……你知道，我不同意……统治。
We voted, and a majority... A majority you know I disagreed with... ruled.
所以我们邀请了大玉米公司GrowSynth，带着他们的除草剂和转基因作物进入我们的田地。
So we invited Big Corn, GrowSynth, right into our fields with their arsenal of herbicides and GMOs.
看看玉米发生了什么。
And look what happened to the corn.
我都不知道。
Just didn't even know.
我的玉米就是这样。
That's what happened to my corn.
-没错。-事情就是这样。
- That's right. - That's what happened.
指责是没有意义的，因为木已成舟。
There's no sense pointing fingers because what's done is done.
但这意味着我们必须面对一个新的现实。
But what that means is we have to face a new reality.
也许，只是也许，所有的手指都指向了错误的方向。
Or maybe, just maybe, all those fingers are pointing the wrong way anyhow.
我们的玉米遭受的枯萎病，也许与GrowSynth或我们放入土壤中的任何转基因生物关系不大，更多的是与我们自己有关，与你们有关。
That blight that struck our corn, maybe it's got a lot less to do with GrowSynth or any GMOs we put in our soil and more to do with us, more to do with you.
坐吧，老头。
Sit down, old man.
也许在我们的玉米地里发生的事情与其说是一场农业灾难不如说是一种道德和精神上的憎恶吞没了这个小镇!
Maybe what's happening out there in our corn is less about an agricultural calamity and more about a moral and spiritual abomination that has engulfed this town!
好吧，既然我们听够了那些道貌不扬的，神圣的滚马废话。
Okay, now that we're done listening to that sanctimonious, Holy Rolling horse crap.
这与你的欺骗和背后的中伤无关。
It isn't about any of the cheating or the backstabbing that's been going on.
它只关乎一件事。
It's about one thing and one thing only.
现在，我们被卖了一大堆豆子。
Now, we was sold a hill of beans.
-没错。——是的!
- That's right. - Yeah!
他们说，我们所要做的就是把这个，把那个放进土壤里，改变我们的玉米，这样我们就可以卖更多的苏打水给第三世界的穷孩子。
All we had to do, they said, was put this put that in the soil and alter our corn so we could sell more soda to the poor kids in the Third World.
他们说，这样做，我们就发财了。
Do that, they said, and we'd be rich.
比我们想象的还要富有。
Richer than we could dream.
但相反，看看发生了什么。
But instead, look at what happened.
玉米病和经济灾难。
Sick corn and economic disaster.
这就是瑞尔斯通必须留下玉米的原因。
And that's why Rylstone has to leave corn behind.
这就是我们能做的。
This is how we can do it.
补贴。
Subsidies.
补贴吗?
Subsidies?
联邦政府将补贴……付给我们……不是种玉米。
Federal government will subsidize... pay us... Not to grow corn.
但这个项目的财政年度还有不到两天就结束了，所以我们必须答应，而且必须现在就做。
But this program's fiscal year ends in less than two days, so we got to say yes and we got to do it now.
我们的推土机就在镇边上准备挖沟埋我们的玉米。
We got earthmovers right at the edge of town ready to dig the trench to bury our corn.
我和你一样不想这样。
And I don't want this any more than you do.
听着，这并不理想，我承认，但我觉得我们别无选择。
And look, it's not ideal, I admit that, but I don't think we have a choice.
好吧，我不同意，爸爸。
Yeah, well, I disagree, Dad.
你们都应该感到羞愧。
You all should be ashamed.
当我们需要你们做成年人的时候，你们没有做成年人，而是帮助了你们自己，给我们留下了创伤。
Instead of being the adults when we needed you to be, you helped yourselves and left the rest of us traumatized.
瑞尔斯通已经出卖过灵魂了。
Rylstone sold its soul once already.
你所做的一切都是为了解决问题，而不是试图修复土壤，是内斗。
And all you're doing to solve the problem, instead of trying to repair the soil, is infighting.
内斗，再一次以最快的速度出卖我们的灵魂，只是卖给了另一个主人。
Infighting and selling all our souls all over again as fast as you can, just to a different master.
但你有选择。
But you do have a choice.
相信我，这不是你要做的事。
Trust me, it's not the one you're making.
我美丽的女儿，波。
My beautiful daughter, Bo.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
一如既往的衷心和热情。
Most heartfelt and passionate, as always.
我希望我能和你一样乐观。
And I wish I shared your optimism.
但试图恢复土壤可能需要数年时间。
But trying to restore the soil could take years.
我们没时间了。
We're simply out of time.
如果你想修复这一切，这破碎的东西…你记住我的话，只会让事情变得更糟。
If you try to fix this, something this broken... you mark my words, you're just going to make it worse.
那我们来投票吧。
So let's put it to a vote.
不，罗伯特，我真的必须……请坐，牧师。没人在乎。
No, Robert, I-I really must... Sit down, Pastor. No one cares.
我同意。让那些脱粒机滚吧。
I say aye. Let those threshers roll.
放开那些大男孩!
Let them big boys go!
是的。佛罗里达分时，我来了。
Yeah. Florida time-share, here I come.
玉米经济见鬼去吧。
Corn economy can kiss my ass.
——是的!——是的!
- Yeah! - Yeah!
看到举手了吗?
See a show of hands?
好吧。我们正在做这件事。每个人的投票。
All right. We're doing this. Everyone's voted.
只是大家都还没投票。
Except everyone hasn't voted.
不是我们。
Not us.
孩子们。
The children.
他们是对的。
They're right.
这也是孩子们的未来。
It's the little ones' futures too.
是啊，他们连投票权都没有。
Yeah, they don't even get a vote, a say.
因为波是对的。我们有一个选择。
'Cause Bo is right. We have a choice.
好了，废话够多了。
All right, enough horseshit.
孩子吗?有发言权?
Children? Having a say?
我以为17岁的孩子顶嘴已经够糟了。
I thought 17-year-olds mouthing off was bad enough.
愚蠢的孩子。
Stupid kids.
听的,听。
Hear, hear.
小孩子!
Little kids!
投票!
Voting!
好吧，我建议你回家玩你的玩具。
Yeah, well, I vote you go home and play with your toys.
好吗，小姑娘?
Okay, little girl?
听起来怎么样?是吗?
How does that sound? Yeah?
你也是，孩子。你就等我回家吧。
You too, boy. You just wait till I get home.
你等着吧，孩子。
You just wait, boy.
嘿，来吧!嘿!嘿!
Hey, come on! Hey! Hey!
看在上帝的份上，那是个孩子。
That's a child, for Christ's sake.
——嘿!-你会没事的。
- Hey! - You're gonna be fine.
好了，别闹了。这就够了。别闹了!
All right, knock it off. That's enough. Knock it off!
你怎么了?
What is wrong with you?
好的。这是解决。
Okay. It's settled.
不到48小时，瑞尔斯通的玉米就会永远消失。
In less than 48 hours, corn will be dead in Rylstone forever.
是的。谢谢你！
Yes. Thank you.
你说的正是我们一直在想的。
You're saying what we've been thinking.
爸爸。
Dad.
听着，事情没必要变成这样。
Listen, it doesn't have to be like this.
现在做点什么还不晚。
It's not too late to do something.
休息一下吧，波。这是完成了。
Give it a rest, Bo. It's done.
你什么时候开始在打架时逃跑了?
Since when do you ever, ever run from a fight?
菠，我能区分争取和合作。
I distinguish, Bo, between fighting for and fighting with.
你说的是瑞尔斯通还是妈妈?
Are you talking about Rylstone or Mom?
怎么啦？它只是…已经结束了，菠。这是结束了。
What? It's just... It's done, Bo. It's over.
这是完成了。
It's done.
你怎么了?
What happened to you?
你以前很不一样。
You used to be so different.
我受够你了!
I have had enough of you!
你得离开这房子!
You need to get out of this house!
滚出这房子!
Get out of this house!
的成年人。
The adults.
我知道。
I know.
它糟透了。
It sucks.
有时候真的很难呼吸。
It's so hard sometimes you can hardly breathe.
但我可以帮忙。
But I can help.
用你的痛苦。
With your pain.
♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我♬他爱我他不爱我
♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not ♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not ♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not ♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not ♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not ♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not
♬他爱我♬他不爱我
♪ He loves me ♪ He loves me not
我父亲认为如果我们试图解决这个问题，只会让事情变得更糟。
My father thinks if we try to fix this, it'll only make things worse.
但他错了。我们可以解决这个问题。
But he's wrong. We can fix this.
这就是…公开的羞辱。
And this is how... Public humiliation.
好吗?
Okay?
我们用图像向世界展示他们对瑞尔斯通，对我们，对玉米做了什么。
We graphically show the world what they did to Rylstone, to us, to the corn.
希拉•博伊斯。
Sheila Boyce.
奥马哈。NowCloud记者。
Omaha. Reporter for NowCloud.
我给她发了短信，告诉她我们的情况，也许她可以报道这个故事，她回复了。
I DM'd her and told her about our situation, that maybe she could cover the story, and she responded.
——什么?-是的。
- What? - Yeah.
你能听懂吗?
So are you with me?
我们要这么做吗?
We doing this?
你要不要?
You in or out?
我们开始吧。
Let's do it.
-是的。-你在开玩笑吗?
- Yeah. - Are you kidding?
我们还在等什么?——好的。
- What are we waiting for? - Okay.
在这里。
Here goes.
喂?嗨。
Hello? Hi.
博林威廉姆斯吗?
Boleyn Williams?
是的,是的!
Yeah, yes!
博伊斯小姐，非常感谢你接我电话。
Miss Boyce, thank you so much for taking my call.
Eden?
耶稣,什么…那是什么?
Jesus, what... what is all that?
血。
Blood.
什么血?
What blood?
迪伦爸爸的猪。
From Dylan's pop's hog.
我们把玉米根涂成红色。
We're painting the corn roots red.
就像红方王后。
Like the Red Queen.
《爱丽丝梦游仙境》。
"Alice in Wonderland."
总得想办法喂玉米。
Got to feed the corn somehow.
好吧，你真的想治好玉米吗?
Okay, so you really you want to heal the corn, huh?
你想拯救玉米吗?好吧。
You want to save the corn? All right.
作为女王，我需要你的帮助。
As the, uh, queen, I need your help.
我需要你和你的朋友们出去，告诉佩妮牧师，告诉你的父母，所有人，所有成年人。
I need you and all your little army of friends to go out, tell Pastor Penny, tell your parents, everyone, all the adults.
有点小谎，对吧?
Kind of fib, okay?
你告诉他们我父亲要召开紧急会议讨论他们要耕种的玉米。
You tell them that my father is calling an emergency meeting about that corn they're gonna plow under.
我要你确保他们今晚十点前到社区大厅。
And I need you to make absolutely sure they're at the community hall by 10:00 p.m. tonight.
你觉得你能做到吗?
Think you can do that?
是的。好的。我会帮你的，菠。
Yeah. Okay. I'll help you do this, Bo.
但为什么是社区大厅呢?
But why the community hall?
哦，因为我们要开庭了。
Oh, 'cause we are gonna have us a trial.
你知道，没有法院是无法进行审判的。
And you know, you can't have a trial without a courthouse.
还有，我们有个从奥马哈来的一流女记者。
Plus, we got this big-time newswoman coming in from Omaha.
所以我要你在进来的路上接她，把她也带到社区大厅。
So I need you to meet her on the road in, bring her to the community hall too.
不要忘记…晚上10点整。
Don't forget... 10:00 p.m. sharp.
待会儿见。
I'll see you later.
来吧。
Come on.
你杀人。
You murderer.
偷偷溜到你身后，用重物压在你脑壳上一劳永逸地结束这一切。
Sneak up behind you and lay something heavy across your skull and end this once and for all.
你是个坏人。你是个很坏的人!
You're a bad man. You're a very bad man!
你这么想。说吧，安东尼。
You think that. Go ahead, Anthony.
我是个很坏的人。继续这么想。
I'm a very bad man. Keep thinking that.
谁从他后面悄悄走过去。
Somebody sneak up behind him.
趁他还在想我，赶紧结束这一切!
Somebody end this now while he's thinking about me!
啊!
Aah!
希望它进入玉米地。
Wish it into the cornfield.
求你了，儿子，祝它到玉米地里去。
Please, son, wish it into the cornfield, please.
好了，我该睡觉了。
Well, beddy-bye for me.
是的。我击败。
Yeah. I'm beat.
你呢，爸爸?
How about you, Dad?
一个还长着丑脸的玩偶。
A jack-in-the-box that still had his bad face.
你不能有不好的想法……别熬夜，好吗?
You mustn't think bad thoughts... Don't stay up too late, okay?
否则我也会对你做同样的事。
Or I'll do the same thing to you.
我们犯了幼稚的错误吗，茜茜?
Are we making a childish mistake, Ceece?
试图改变世界从来都不是错误，菠。
It's never a mistake to try and change the world, Bo.
你们在做什么?
What are you guys doing?
爸爸，你还记得你告诉过我有些事值得为之奋斗吗?
Dad, you know how you told me some things are worth fighting for?
我猜你养育我的方式是对的，因为现在就是这样。
Well, I guess you raised me right, because that's what's happening.
我们要举行模拟审判，而你是主宾。
We're holding a mock trial, and you're the guest of honor.
别吵醒妈妈。
Don't wake Mom.
悄悄地来，我保证很快就会结束的。
Come quietly, and I promise you this will be over soon.
你确定吗，菠?
You sure about this, Bo?
拜托，考尔德。我们已经迟到了。
Yeah, come on, Calder. We're already late.
大家都去哪儿了?
Where is everyone?
不，没关系。相信我。
No, it's okay. Trust me.
你好,Bo。
Hi, Bo.
Eden。
Eden.
每个人都在哪儿?记者在哪里?
Where's everybody? Where's the reporter?
希拉•博伊斯。
Sheila Boyce.
谁?
Who?
记者。从奥马哈。
The reporter. From Omaha.
你应该去接她的。
You were supposed to pick her up.
她没有出现。
She never showed.
我猜肯定有更重要的事情发生了。
Guess something more important must have come up.
她……
Did she...
已经不重要了，菠。
Doesn't really matter anymore, Bo.
这是结束了。
It's over.
是什么?在是什么?
What is? What's over?
你迟到了。
You were late.
所以我们就这么做了。
So we just went ahead and did it.
你做了什么?
You did what?
的审判。
The trial.
父母呢?
Where are the parents?
大家都去哪儿了?
Where is everyone?
凸轮。
Cam.
爸爸在哪儿?
Where's Dad?
到底是怎么回事?
What the hell is going on?
想看点什么吗，波?
Want to see something, Bo?
我猜他不同意判决结果。
Didn't agree with the verdict, I guess.
跟这种人相处总是需要付出更多，菠。
It was always gonna take more with these kind of people, Bo.
还有很多。
A lot more.
考尔德!
Calder!
爸爸?爸爸!
Dad? Dad!
帮帮我!提他!把他举起来!
Help me! Lift him! Lift him up!
提升!提他!
Lift! Lift him!
我们走吧。
Let's go.
爸爸!
Dad!
爸爸。
Dad.
不!不!不!不!
No! No! No! No!
他现在不笑了。
He's not laughing now.
看看我们!
Check us out!
是啊!
Yeah!
来吧!来吧!
Come on! Come on!
这太离谱了!
This is outrageous!
我发誓，地狱之火会倾盆而下。
I swear, it's gonna rain down with hellfire.
我在跟你说话，伊登。
I'm talking to you, Eden.
Eden,亲爱的……现在回头还不晚。
Eden, honey... It's not too late to turn back.
你现在是我女儿了。
You're my daughter now.
你认为你应该这样做吗?
Do you think this is how you should behave?
这该死的!
God damn!
还有问题吗?
Any more questions?
我不这么认为。
I didn't think so.
-你没事吧?-是的。
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
这太疯狂了。这完全是疯狂的。
This is insanity. This is completely insane.
你看到外面的情况了吗?
Did you see what it was like out there?
所有的尸体。
All the dead bodies.
我不知道我父母在哪。
I don't know where my parents are.
我不知道他们怎么了。
I don't know what happened to them.
让我们把这地方翻个底朝天!
Let's tear this place to the ground!
我的电话。我的手机坏了。
My phone. My phone doesn't work.
我的。
Mine either.
这些小怪物会不会对信号塔做了什么?
Could these little freaks have done something to the cell tower?
耶稣。
Jesus.
我哥哥现在和他们在一起。
My brother is with them now.
把他们撕碎!
Rip 'em up!
薄薄
Bo. Bo.
做点什么。
Do something.
如果可以，请帮助我们。
Help us if you can.
打击他们!
Hit 'em!
我们必须这么做。我们……我们可以做点什么。
We have to. We... We can do something.
看看这个!
Look at this!
是的,Bo。
Yes, Bo.
你是对的。我们必须阻止这一切。
You're right. We have to stop this.
——啊!——不!
- Aaaah! - No!
我的上帝。
My God.
Eden。
Eden.
耶稣基督。你想在这里做什么?
Jesus Christ. What is it you intend to do here?
嗯…
Well...
如果你真的想知道的话。
If you really want to know.
我希望你能比蒂米·凯恩，艾娃·福斯特，博伊德·鲍登，或者我其他的不良朋友更能屏住呼吸。
I hope you can hold your breath better than Timmy Cain, Ava Foster, Boyd Bowden, or any of my other delinquent friends.
不!
No!
氟烷!
It's halothane!
捂住嘴!
Cover your mouths!
Eden,不!
Eden, no!
Eden!
这是给我朋友的。感觉如何?
This is for my friends. How does it feel?
你觉得怎么样?
How do you like it?
你好，格布勒警长。
Heya, Sheriff Gebler.
妈妈?
Mom?
看在上帝的份上，你以为你在干什么?
What in God's name do you think you're doing?
做出裁决。
Rendering the verdict.
你就等着我抓到你吧。
You just wait till I get my hands on you.
你这个小贱人。
You little, bitch.
哦!真的吗?
Oh! Really?
你想惹我吗?
You want to mess with me?
是的。好的,很好。是的。让我们玩。
Yeah. Okay, fine. Yeah. Let's play.
史蒂夫!乔!我们走吧!
Steve! Joe! Let's go!
Eden。
Eden.
-伊登，不要，求你了。-你没必要这么做。
- Eden, no, please. - You don't have to do this.
不!你不能这么做!
No! You can't do this!
Eden。Eden!
Eden. Eden!
让我们出去!
Let us out!
停!
Stop!
博,不!
Bo, no!
妈妈!
Mom!
不!
No!
你在干什么?!
What are you doing?!
不,不!
No, no!
停!
Stop!
不，别这么做!
No, don't do it!
停!不!
Stop! No!
不!
No!
妈妈!妈妈!
Mom! Mom!
塞西尔。
Cecil.
饲料。
Feed.
妈妈。
Mom.
我很抱歉。
I am sorry.
我爸爸是对的。
My dad was right.
他警告我，如果我想弥补，只会让事情更糟。
He warned me if I tried to fix this I'd only make it worse.
所以，如果可以的话，就出去吧。
So get out if you can.
拯救自己。
Save yourselves.
但是我爸爸还活着。
But my dad is still alive.
所以我要留下来阻止伊登把他也杀了。
So I'm gonna stay and stop Eden from killing him too.
是的。
Yeah.
好的。
Okay.
好的,Bo。
Okay, Bo.
去烛台吧。
Well, go to Candlestick.
寻求帮助。
And get help.
你好,Bo。
Hi, Bo.
伊登，你不能。
Eden, you can't.
你不能这样做。
You cannot do this.
他们杀了他们碰过的所有东西。
They kill everything they touch.
让他们接受审判是你的主意。
Putting them on trial was your idea.
你以为会发生什么?
What did you think would happen?
不是这个。
Not this.
是我们对他们。
It's us against them.
你站在哪一边?
Whose side are you on?
你要拿我父亲和其他人怎么办?
What are you gonna do with my father and the others?
我要把他们送到玉米地里去，菠。
I'm gonna send them out to the corn, Bo.
他生病了。他需要进食。
He's sick. He needs to feed.
他吗?
He?
行走的人。
He Who Walks.
我在那里的那个星期……
That week I was out there...
独自在玉米地里游荡……他跟我说话了。
wandering alone in the corn... he talked to me.
他照顾我。
He took care of me.
瑞尔斯通没有一个成年人为我这样做过。
No adult in Rylstone ever did that for me.
所以现在我要照顾他。
So now I'm going to take care of him.
杀死所有的成年人?
By killing all the adults?
首先。
For starters.
波，他们吃了玉米种子。
They ate the seed-corn, Bo.
现在是时候付出代价了。
Now it's time to pay the price.
如果我们中有人能离开这里，去烛台，我们就能得到帮助，好吗?
If one of us can just get out of here, make it to Candlestick, we can get help, all right?
看看这个!
Check this out!
这太疯狂了。爸爸，我需要你相信我。
This is insanity. Dad, I need you to trust me.
现在，他们想知道我站在哪一边，所以我需要你完全按我说的做。
Right now, they want to know who's side I'm on, so I need you to do exactly what I say.
听着，他们想带你们去玉米地里。
Listen, they want to take you all out into the corn.
——什么?对什么?——走吧!走吧!
- What? What for? - Go! Go!
你会很安全的。你可以寻求帮助。
You'll be safe. You can get help.
如果那个生物想让我们去玉米地里，那我们就应该做完全相反的事!
If that creature wants us to go into the corn, then we should be doing the exact opposite!
我不会担心的。
I wouldn't worry about it.
反正你也不会去玉米地里。
You were never going into the corn anyway.
因为你挺身而出
Because you stood up for it.
是的。没错，伊登。
Yes. That's right, Eden.
玉米的死跟我一点关系都没有。
I never had a thing to do with killing the corn.
事实上，我强烈反对!
In fact, I-I spoke out strongly against it!
伊登，还记得在寄养家庭发生的事吗?
Eden, remember that thing that happened in the foster home?
哦。谁收留了你?
Ohh. Who took you in, hmm?
是你，牧师。你所做的。
It was you, Pastor. You did.
你收留了我。
You took me in.
你从未像其他人那样对谷物犯过罪。
You never sinned against the corn like all the rest.
但是，拜托，牧师。
But, come on, Pastor.
你犯了罪。
You did sin.
不是吗?
Didn't you?
——够了!-闭嘴。
- Enough! - Shut up.
不!
No!
不,Eden!不，求你了，不要!
No, Eden! No, please, no!
不，伊登，不!
No, Eden, no!
不，不，不，不!
No, no, no, no!
不，伊登，不!
No, Eden, no!
上帝!哦，天哪，不!
God! Oh, God, no!
拜托!
Please!
不,Eden!
No, Eden!
不,不!
No, no!
天啊，不，不!
God, no, no!
哦,Eden…
Oh, Eden...
波，她在哪?
Bo, where is she?
求你了，别问我这个。别问我妈妈的事。
Please, don't ask me that. Don't ask me about Mom.
我要知道我妻子在哪里!
I need to know where my wife is!
停!
Stop!
听着，你得去玉米地里。
Listen, you need to go out to the corn.
就是这样。这是我们寻求帮助的机会。
That's it. This is our chance to get help.
好吧?就是它了。
Okay? This is it.
好的。我去。
Okay. I'll go.
但你会战斗。好吧?
But you fight. All right?
是的。
Yes.
我爱你。
I love you.
我也爱你。
I love you too.
你做得很好。
You did good.
他今晚会吃得很饱的。
He'll feed well tonight.
放下枪，小卡。
Drop it, Cam.
她不是威胁。
She's not a threat.
好的,爸爸。
Okay, Dad.
我会的。
I will.
我会战斗。
I will fight.
猜猜还有什么。
And guess what else.
从现在起，里尔斯通不许任何人出入!
From now on, no one in Rylstone and no one out!
如果有人想在这里停下来，猜猜我们要做什么。
And if anyone cares to stop here, guess what we're gonna do.
带他们!把他们带到玉米地里去!
Take them! Take them into the corn!
这是正确的。把它们放到玉米地里。
That's right. Get them into the corn.
因为我们不需要他们提供的任何东西!
Because we don't need a single thing they have to offer!
我们需要的一切都在这里，就在那片田野里。
Everything we've ever needed is right here, right out there in those fields.
玉米，土地，会照顾它的孩子。
The corn, the earth, will take care of its children.
现在这是我们的世界，我们要改变一下，按我们想要的方式经营。
This is our world now, and we're gonna run it the way we want for a change.
我们要好好经营!
And we're gonna run it right!
没错!
Right!
也不只是瑞尔斯通一个人。
And isn't just gonna be Rylstone either.
我们要把消息传遍全国。
We're gonna spread the word all across this country.
你以为没有像我们这样的人吗?
You think there aren't others like us?
孩子们眼睁睁地看着自己的世界和未来被出卖?
Kids seeing their world and future just being traded away?
他们也会夺回自己的城镇，让整个世界恢复正常!
Well, they're gonna take their towns, too, and make this whole world right again!
——对吧!——对吧!
- Right! - Right!
比如这个。
Like this thing.
它要利用我们，要出卖我们的未来。
It was going to use us, was going to sell our future.
所以我们应该把她的头砍下来，对吧，菠?
So we should cut her head off, right, Bo?
不!
No!
我的意思是，是的。
I mean, yes.
是的。
Yes.
她犯了罪。
She sinned.
她得罪了你。
She sinned against you.
对我们所有人。
Against all of us.
所以我们不应该在这里浪费她的血。
And that's why we shouldn't waste her blood here.
我可以把她送到玉米地里去。
Not when I can send her into the corn.
这是个好主意，菠。
That's a pretty good idea, Bo.
但是,博…
But, Bo...
更好的办法是直接带她去见他。
An even better idea would be to take her straight to him.
这里。
This way.
就是这样。
That's it.
带她上去。
Take her up.
门。
Doors.
行走的人!
He Who Walks!
来了!
Come!
到我们这儿来!
Come to us!
Eden。
Eden.
那个行走的人，他不存在。
He Who Walks, he doesn't exist.
你竟敢这么说!
Don't you dare say that!
待回来。
Stay back.
这不可能是真的。
It can't be real.
啊!
Aah!
帮帮我!
Help me!
你伤不了我的，菠。
You can't hurt me, Bo.
天啊，你们这些白痴!你们这些该死的小白痴!
God, you idiots! You're goddamn little idiots!
振作起来。
Brace yourself.
你是…你疯了吗?!
Are you... Are you crazy?!
粮食粉尘。
Grain dust.
还记得吗?
Remember?
这地方到处都是。
This place is full of it.
你一点火，这地方就会被炸飞。
You light a fire, this whole place will blow sky high.
玉米和里面的东西都会烧起来。
The corn and everything in it will burn.
很好。
Fine.
我们把她剁了吧。
Let's chop her up.
继续。得到她。
Go on. Get her.
来吧!
Come on!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
到玉米地里去!
Into the corn!
来吧!
Come on!
爸爸。
Dad.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
帮助我。
Help me.
车!是的!
Car! Yes!
钥匙，钥匙，钥匙。
Keys, keys, keys.
去他妈的。
Fuck that shit.
不。不。
No. No.
不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
哦，谢谢。哦，谢天谢地。
Oh, thank you. Oh, thank God.
你好,Bo。
Hi, Bo.
Eden。
Eden.
Eden,Eden。
Eden, Eden.
耶稣。
Jesus.
这……这太疯狂了。
T-This... This is madness.
疯狂,疯狂。
Craziness, insanity.
你知道吗?
You know?
是的。这太疯狂了。
Yeah. It's pretty crazy.
我会告诉你的。
I'll give you that.
那是什么，伊登?
What is that, Eden?
哦。
Oh.
这一点。
This.
肯定的，菠。
Depositive bolt, Bo.
你知道，牛枪。
You know, a cattle gun.
我知道你在想什么。
I know what you're thinking.
算了吧。
Forget it.
你知道这里不止我一个人。
You know I'm not the only one out here.
已经过了我的就寝时间。
It's past my bedtime.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
至少最后一根烟?
A l-last cigarette at least?
你抽烟吗?
You smoke?
坏习惯。我…正要辞职。
Bad habit. I... was about to quit.
来吧。
Come on.
跪下来。
Get down on your knees.
别害怕，菠。
Don't be scared, Bo.
嘿,Eden?
Hey, Eden?
你真的以为你把我浸在拖拉机燃料里的那一刻，我就不会确定我的结果是正确的…
You really think the second you soaked me in all that tractor fuel, that I wasn't gonna make sure I ended up right...
在这里吗?
here?
燃烧。
Burn.
不。
No.
不，不，不!
No, no, no!
烛台和方圆几英里内的其他人很快就会到这里。
Candlestick and everyone else for miles around will be here soon.
面对它。
Face it.
结束了。
It's done.
你的幻想结束了，伊登。
Your fantasy's finished, Eden.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
Eden。
Eden.
别担心，波。
Don't worry, Bo.
在玉米地里什么都不会死。
Nothing ever really dies in the corn.